# DORIGATTI ASSAN

**FEDERICO** 

# **Full-Stack Developer**

I dedicate myself exclusively to web programming for 2 years and I have been I have been studying programming for 7 years. Lately I am acquiring knowledge with node.js structures, ejs engine Outstanding in the sector, for designing a front-end dynamic, attractive, modern and above all, interactive and intuitive for the user.

On the other hand, I have been developing relational tables for more than 4 years. (sql, mariadb, alwasdata), the technological advance made it incorporate tables non-relational (mongodb, mongoose) to incorporate I carry out a react course applying this type of table.

### **Personal details**

Name
Federico Dorigatti Assan

Address

Av. Cristobal Colon 2187

Mar del Plata, B7600FYB

**Phone** (+54) 1141761096

**Emails** doriass.f@gmail.com

Birthdate
1/9/1998
Place of birth

Sgo. del Estero(Arg)

Linkedin.com /in/desarrrolladorfrontendbackend/

Briefcase vercel
https://portafolio-xi-ten.vercer.app/

## Work experience

**Freelance** paginasweb.io, Mar del Plata jun 2023 - present **Full-Stack** Digital desing, Mar del Plata sep. 2022 - jun. 2023 developer nd.is **Premises** Drugstore Argentina, Mar del Plata mar 2022 - may. 2023 manager Sales Rapi-Coutas, Tucumán sep. 2021 - feb. 2022 and charges of loans

#### Education

### **Programming degree**

Universidad Tecnologica Nacional, San Miguel de Tucuman

Grades: 7.40/10 pts Asignaturas: 17/25 Duration: 3 years

Content: C+, Web, Genexus, Robotica, Contabilidad, Matematica, Legislacion..

# kin Node.js & React.js

Codo a Codo, Buenos Aires

Grades: 9/10 pts Duration:1 year

Content: Desarrollar app web con estructuras node.js y vistas react. Ademas utilizar

bases de datos no relacionales.

## Skin

html
css
javascript
php

node.js
express.js
ejs
react

tailwilnd.css
bootstrap
vanilla

#### Work to do

Create and update custom web applications, design, layout, develop and implement databases. Works with node js structures, with spreadsheet styles, coded designs without the need for external libraries, elegant, attractive, dynamic, and above all intuitive and dynamic.

#### Certificate



Python, fullstak



Frot-end, developer



ene. 2020 - dic. 2023

ene. 2023 - dic. 2023